Finding Aid for Jennifer Granholm papers, 1992-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Legal Division
  - Steven C. Liedel: Deputy Legal Counsel (2003-2008) and Legal Counsel (2008-2010)
    - Executive Orders, Directives, and Proclamations
      - Executive Order 2007-43, Michigan Interagency Coordinating Council for Infants and Toddlers with Developmental Disabilities (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-44, Creation of the Michigan Food Policy Council (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-45, Revoking Declaration of Financial Emergency For City of Hamtramck (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-46, Michigan Juvenile Accountability Block Grant Advisory Board (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-47, Establishing the Michigan Intelligence Operations Center for Homeland Security (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-48, Michigan Rehabilitation Council (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-49, Statewide Independent Living Council (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-50, Idlewild Centennial Commission (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-51, Michigan commission on the Commemoration of the Bicentennial of the War of 1812 (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-52, Observing the Sesquicentennial of the Civil War (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-53, State Historic Preservation Office and Review Board (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2007-54, State Historical Records Advisory Board (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-1, Restrictions on Purchase of Non-Essential Supplies, Materials, Equipment, Printing, or Other Products (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-2, Restrictions on Service Contracts and Use of Temporary Employees (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-3, Restrictions on Nonessential Travel (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-4, Efficient Use of State Motor Vehicle Fleet and Reduction in Vehicle Travel Expenditures (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-5, Reduction of State Expenditures for Telecommunications (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-6, Reduction of Energy Usage (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-7, Restrictions on Expenditures for Membership in Associations and Organizations (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-8, Reduction of State Expenditures for Periodical Subscriptions and Other Subscription Services (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-9, Reduction of State Expenditures for Acquisition of Space for State Operations (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-10, Special Monitor for State Purchasing (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-11, Moratorium on State Grant Expenditures (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-12, Moratorium on State Employee Training Expenditures (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-13, Moratorium on Statewide Hiring, Creation of New Positions, Filling Vacant Positions, Transfer, and Promotions (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-14, Moratorium on Performance Pay Awards (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-15, Collecting Revenue Payable to the State of Michigan (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-16, Reduction of State Expenditures for Periodical Subscriptions and Other Subscription Services (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-17, Restrictions on Purchase of Non-Essential Supplies, Materials, Equipment, Printing, or Other Products (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-18, Moratorium on Service Contracts and Use of Temporary Employees (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-19, Travel Moratorium (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-20, Preparation for Shutdown of State Government Operations (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-21, Extension of Fiscal Austerity Measures (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-22, Enhanced energy Efficiency and Conservation by State Departments and Agencies (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-23, Promoting Environmental Justice (Box 33)
      - Executive Directive 2007-24, Equal Opportunity in State Employment (Box 33)
      - Proclamation 2007-2, Partially Rescinding the Ban on the Use of Fire on Forest Lands and Adjacent Lands in Certain Counties (Box 33)
      - Proclamation 2007-3, Rescinding the Ban on the Use of Fire on Forest Lands and Adjacent Lands in the Lower Peninsula (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2008-1, Employee Misclassification Task Force (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2008-2, Executive Reorganization -- Office of Financial and Insurance Regulation (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2008-3, Amendment of Executive Order 2003-2 (Box 33)
      - Executive Order 2008-4, Declaration of State of Emergency Mason County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-5, Declaration of State of Emergency City of Lansing, Ingham County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-6, Declaration of State of Emergency Allegan County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-7, Declaration of State of Emergency Eaton County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-8, Declaration of State of Emergency City of Saginaw, Saginaw County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-9, Activation of National Guard to Cities of Lansing and Saginaw and to Counties of Allegan, Eaton, and Mason (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-10, Amendment of Executive Order 2008-4 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-11, Amendment of Executive Order 2008-6 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-12, Declaration of State of Emergency Osceola County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-13, Declaration of State of Emergency Ottawa County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-14, Declaration of State of Emergency Lake County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-15, Declaration of State of Emergency Wexford County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-16, Declaration of State of Emergency Manistee County (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-17, Abolishing the Criminal Justice Information Systems Policy Council (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-18, Department of Corrections Michigan Prisoner Reentry Advisory Council (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-19, Amendment of Executive Order 2001-5 Michigan Commission on Law Enforcement Standards (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-20, Creation of Department of Energy, Labor, and Economic Growth (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-21, Executive Order 2008-21, Implementation of Expenditure Reductions for the Fiscal Year Ending September 30, 2009 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-22, State Equal Opportunity and Diversity Council (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-23, Motor Carrier Safety Assistance Program (Box 34)
      - Executive Directive 2008-1, Protecting the Safety of Highway Construction Workers (Box 34)
      - Executive Directive 2008-2, Annual Observance of Michigan Week (Box 34)
      - Executive Orders 2008-4-2008-11, Emergency Management (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2008-20, Creation of Department of Energy, Labor, and Economic Growth (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-1, Great Lakes Wind Council (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-2, Department of Community Health Executive Reorganization (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-3, Office of Long-Term Care Supports and Services (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-4, Department of Agriculture Department of Management and Budget Executive Reorganization (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-5, Creation of Michigan Parole and Commutation Board (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-6, Department of Agriculture Department of Energy, Labor and Economic Growth Executive Reorganization (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-7, Abolishing the Campground Public Health Advisory Board (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-8, Abolishing the Clinical Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-9, Abolishing the Grantee Health Agency Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-10, Abolishing the Hearing and Vision Programs Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-11, Abolishing the Poison Control Center Network Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-12, Abolishing the Sanitarian Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-13, Abolishing the PBDE Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-14, Abolishing the Citizen’s Advisory Committee for Natural Beauty Roads (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-15, Abolishing the public Boating Access Site Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-16, Rescission of Executive Order 2009-7 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-17, Abolishing the Campground Public Health Advisory Board (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-18, Creation of a Chief Privacy Officer and Information Privacy Protection Council (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-19, Amendment of Executive Order 2009-1 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-20, Amendment of Executive Order 2009-5 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-21, New Asian Pacific American Affairs Commission (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-22, Implementation of Expenditure Reductions Under Section 20 of Article V of the Michigan Constitution of 1963 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-23, Amendment of Executive Order 2009-17 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-24, Abolishing the Reflex Sympathetic Dystrophy/Complex Regional Pain Syndrome Work Group (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-25, Abolishing Private Sector Advisory Task Force (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-26, Abolishing Siting Criteria Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-27, Abolishing Substance Abuse Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-28, Abolishing the Interdepartmental Medical Waste Advisory Council (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-29, Abolishing the Third party Administrator Advisory Board (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-30, Amendment of Executive Order 2007-47 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-31, Abolishing the Advisory Subcommittee on Interior Design (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-32, Abolishing the Michigan Housing and Community Development Fund Advisory Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-33, Transferring School Building Construction, Reconstruction, Remodeling and site Plan Approval Functions (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-34 2010 United States Census Complete Count Committee (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-35, Michigan Economic Recovery Office, Michigan Economic Recovery Oversight Board, Executive Office of the Governor, Department of Management and Budget (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-36, Abolition of the Department of History, Arts, and Libraries (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-37, Declaration of Emergency for Federal Highway Assistance (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-38, Rescission of Executive Order 2009-23 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-39, Amendment of Executive Order 2009-17 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-40, Disability Concerns Commission (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-41, Amendment of Executive Order 2005-6 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-42, Department of Community Health Department of State Policy Department of Education Executive Reorganization (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-43, Amending Executive Order 2009-36 (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-44, Abolishing the Michigan Climate Action Council Abolishing the Aquatic Nuisance Species Council (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-45, Creating the Department of Natural Resource and Environment (Box 34)
      - Executive Order 2009-46, Amendment of Executive Order 2009-1 (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-47, Abolishing the Building Officials Advisory Board (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-48, Abolishing the Advisory Committee for Development of Educational Television System (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-49, Abolishing the Public Transit Association Task Force (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-50, Abolishing the Michigan Telecommunications Relay Service Advisory Board (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-51, Department of Treasury Executive Reorganization (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-53, Amendment of Executive Order 2003-18 (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-54, Commission of Agriculture (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2009-55, Creation of the Department of Technology, Management, and Budget (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2009-1, Fair and Equitable Automobile Insurance Rates (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2009-2, Consideration of Feasible and Prudent Alternatives In the Processing of Air Permit Applications from Coal-Fired Power Plants (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2009-3, Reduction in Contractual Expenditures, Moratorium on Personal Services Contract Expenditures, and Restrictions on the Use of Temporary Employees (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2009-4, Implementation of Recommendations of the Michigan climate Action Council (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2009-5, Implementation of Executive Order 2009-36 (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2009-6, Implementation of Executive Order 2009-45 (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2010-1, Cost-Effective Health Care Benefits for Employees of Public Entities in Michigan (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2010-2, Michigan Economic Growth Authority (Box 35)
      - Executive Directive 2010-3, Implementation of Recommendations of the Michigan Information Privacy Protection Council (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-1, Creation of Office of Health Services Inspector General (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-2, Creation of Michigan Finance Authority (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-3, Michigan Economic Growth Authority (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-4, Implementation of the Patient Protection and Affordable Care Act (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-5, Michigan Center for Innovation and Reinvention Board (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-6, Declaration of State of Emergency -- Monroe County (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-7, Declaration of State of Disaster -- Calhoun County Oil Spill (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-8, Abolishing the Strategic Economic Investment and Commercialization Board (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-9, Manufactured Housing Commission (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-10, Board of Health and Safety Compliance Appeals (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-11, Abolishing the Renewable Fuels Commission (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-12, Abolishing the Mentor Michigan Leadership Council (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-13, Abolishing the Michigan Center for Innovation and Reinvention Board (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-14, Abolishing the Complete Count Committee (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-15, Creating the P-20 Longitudinal Data System Advisory Council (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-16, Abolishing the Center for Educational Performance and Information Advisory Committee (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-17, Abolishing the Foster Care Trust Fund Board (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-18, Governor’s Task Force on child Abuse and Neglect (Box 35)
      - Executive Order 2010-19, Executive Office of the Governor Department of Technology, Management, and Budget Executive Reorganization (Box 35)
    - Legislation 2007-2008
      - HB 4483 and HB 4484 2003, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - SB 195 2003-2004 (Box 35)
      - HB 4610 Video Lottery Terminals 2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 1279 State Park Check Off 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 432, Michigan Election Law 2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 4187 Pay Phone Rate Quotes 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 4478 Parental Consent 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 4511 Administrative Rules 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 4610 Racinos 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 5029 Dove Hunting 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 5113 County Commissioners 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 5190 HR Consolidation 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 5479 77th District Judgeship 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 5480 55th Circuit Judgeship 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 5554 Forest Audit 2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 6028 Absentee Voting 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 189, Community Health Continuing Education 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 195, Detroit Water 2003-2004, 2 folders (Box 36)
      - SB 320, Youth Employment Hours 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - HB 4455 Jury Duty Deferment for Caregivers of Small Children 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 252 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 395, Partial Birth Abortion 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 474, Payday Lending 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 647, Michigan Office of Safety and Health Administration (MIOSHA) 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 687, Oakland County Executive 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 700, Detroit Delinquent Taxes 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 721, Recycling Fee 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 785, License Plates 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 800, Regulatory Reform 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 822 and MEGA SBT 389, Single Business Tax 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 824, Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA) 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 840, Small Business Czar 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 841, Manufacturing Czar 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 849, Brownfield 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 867, Bill Analysis 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 872, Bill Analysis 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 905, Fire fighters Training Council 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 998, Drug Treatment Courts 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 1062 Return of Enrolled Bill 2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 889, Child Support Workers’ Compensation 2003-2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 1093 Creation of New Jobs 2004 (Box 36)
      - SB 1130 State Fair 2003-2004 (Box 37)
      - SB 432, Help America Vote Act (HAVA) 2003-2004, 3 folders (Box 37)
      - HB 4275 Board of State Canvassers 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Cell Phone Records 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Detroit Area Regional Transportation Authority (DARTA) 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - SB 513, Digitized Signatures 2005 (Box 37)
      - HB 5447 Ergonomics 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Fire Service 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Human Trafficking 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Inactive Voter Files 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - HB 4636 Item Pricing 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Kreiner 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Mackinac Bridge Authority 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Minimum Wage 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - HB 5028 and HB 5029 Port Authority 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - HB 4849 Real Estate Professionals 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Rule Against Perpetuities 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - SB 957, Single Business Tax 2005-2006 (Box 37)
      - Single Business Tax Repeal 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Section 131e, Hearings 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - SB 248, Speed Limits 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - State Officer’s Compensation Commission 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Bills Package 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Travel Promotion 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Video Franchising 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Water Legacy Act 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - SB 252, Wolverine Pipeline 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - SB 272, FY 2005-2006 Supplemental, 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Mackinac Bridge Authority 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Jobs Today
        - Schools 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - Michigan State Housing Development Authority (MSHDA) 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - Environmental 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - Nursing Homes 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - Transportation 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - Downtown Development Authority (DDA)/TIFAS 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - New Merit (Michigan Merit Award) 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - State Building Authority (SBA) 2005-2006 (Box 38)
        - General 2005-2006 (Box 38)
      - Jobs for Michigan Fund
        - Constitution 1963 Article 12, Section 1, 2004-2005 (Box 38)
        - Michigan Strategic Fund Act (MSF) 2005-2006, 2 folders (Box 38)
        - Clean Michigan Initiative (CMI) 1998 (Box 38)
        - Jobs Tomorrow 2005-2006 (Box 39)
        - Other States 2005-2006 (Box 39)
        - Media 2005 (Box 39)
        - Alternatives 1997-2001 (Box 39)
      - Jobs Package
        - SB 1132 2005-2006 (Box 39)
        - Constitution 1963 Article 9.S19 Permanent Fund, 2005 (Box 39)
        - Michigan Strategic Fund Act 2005-2006 (Box 39)
        - Other Acts 1966-2003 (Box 39)
        - SB 488 2005 (Box 39)
        - SB 533 2005 (Box 39)
        - HB 5005 2005 (Box 39)
        - HB 5048 2005 (Box 39)
      - Township Vacancies 2005-2006 (Box 39)
      - HB 5109 Michigan Trust Fund Act 2005 (Box 39)
      - HB 5215 Single Business Tax, Act 2005 (Box 39)
      - HB 5216 Income Tax Act of 1967, 2005 (Box 39)
      - Corporate Responsibility Package 2005-2006 (Box 39)
      - SB 372, Detroit Water and Sewer 2005-2006 (Box 39)
      - Ethics Package 2005-2006, 3 folders (Box 39)
      - Business Courts 2005-2006 (Box 40)
      - Child Support Guidelines 2005-2006 (Box 40)
      - HB 5047 Jobs Package 2005-2006, 3 folders (Box 40)
      - Budget Reform Issues
        - Campaign Finance Reform 2007-2008 (Box 40)
        - Commission on Legislative Mandates 2007-2008 (Box 40)
        - Ethics Reform 2007-2008 (Box 40)
        - General Reforms 2007-2008 (Box 40)
        - HB 4600-4601 Retiree Health Care Fund 2007-2008 (Box 40)
        - SB 396, Commission on Government Efficiency 2007-2008 (Box 40)
        - State Vehicles Reform 2007-2008 (Box 40)
      - Revenue Issues
        - Income Tax 2007-2008 (Box 40)
        - Continuation and Budget 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - Loopholes 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - General 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - Sales Tax 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - Services Tax 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - HB 4563 Border Development and Protection Authority 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Detroit Wayne County Port Authority 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Driver’s License 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Film Incentives
        - Production Tax Credit-Michigan Business Tax (MBT) 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5841/SB 1168 40% Production Credit (MBT) 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5842/SB 1169 Phase-Out Old Production Credit (Sales Tax) 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5843/SB 1170 Amend 1944 PA 22 (Revenue Act), 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5844/SB 1171 Claim 40% Production Credit Against Withholding Tax (Income Tax) 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5845/SB 1172 Investment Rollover Exemption (Income Tax) 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5846/SB 1173 Infrastructure Investment Credit (MBT) 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5847/SB 1174 Michigan Economic Growth Authority (MEGA) Eligibility 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5848/SB 1175 Film Loan Programs, Michigan Strategic Fund (MSF) Act 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5849/SB 1176 Job Training Tax Credit (MBT) (Box 41)
        - HB 5850/SB 1177 Transfer & Strengthen Film Office 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5851/SB 1178 State Property Use (DMB Act) 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5852/SB 1179 Military Property Use 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5853/SB 1180 DNR Property Use 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5854/SB 1181 MDOT Property Use 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5855/SB 1182 Local Government Property Use 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - HB 5856/SB 1183 History, Arts, and Libraries (HAL) Act Amendments 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - General 2007-2008, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Louisiana 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - General Sales Tax Act 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - Summaries 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - Connecticut 2007-2008 (Box 41)
        - New Mexico 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Health Care 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Healthcare Plan 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Legal Defense Fund 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Lobbying Reform 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Lottery Privatization 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Michigan Trust Fund Act Amendments 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - Paygo 2007-2008 (Box 41)
      - HB 5690 Incorporation of Regional Convention Authorities 2008
        - General, 2 folders (Box 41)
        - Cobo Hall (Box 42)
        - Legislation (Box 42)
        - Statutes (Box 42)
        - Financials (Box 42)
        - City of Detroit Plan (Box 42)